<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About the Global Carbon Reward on Global Carbon Reward</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/</link><description>Recent content in About the Global Carbon Reward on Global Carbon Reward</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Our Vision</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-vision/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-vision/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="our-vision"&gt;Our Vision&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our vision is a world with a safe climate, together with healthy ecosystems, vibrant communities, and reliable clean energy.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id="three-strategic-pillars"&gt;Three Strategic Pillars&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="1-resolve"&gt;1. Resolve&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The organization aims to address the climate crisis through incentive-based mechanisms combining &amp;ldquo;carrot and stick&amp;rdquo; approaches for climate mitigation. This centers on a novel pricing theory for carbon and proposes carbon rewards to finance climate action and associated benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="2-coordinate"&gt;2. Coordinate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal involves aligning governments, markets, and citizens toward collaborative climate management, ecosystem protection, and social advancement. This relies on establishing a global carbon reward marketplace and stakeholder engagement through reward weighting preferences.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Our Mission</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-mission/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-mission/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="our-mission"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Our mission is to demonstrate and advocate a regenerative financial system that can advance a low-carbon transition while promoting ecological health, community wellbeing, and energy reliability.&amp;rdquo; (Updated January 18, 2025)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="four-core-tasks"&gt;Four Core Tasks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The organization commits to completing these objectives:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Establish demonstrations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advocate the policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Propose a multilateral governance architecture&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id="detailed-focus-areas"&gt;Detailed Focus Areas&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="demonstrations"&gt;Demonstrations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The organization prioritizes developing Global Carbon Reward showcases featuring diverse low-carbon technologies through public-private partnerships. These initiatives illustrate how governments can fund climate action without direct taxation and demonstrate how international cost-sharing conflicts can be resolved through a global climate mitigation services market. The demonstrations emphasize stakeholder consensus based on outcome ranking and financial incentives for improved people and planet results.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Our Plan</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-plan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-plan/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="our-plan"&gt;Our Plan&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our goal is to advocate and advance the Global Carbon Reward policy with our international partners, by demonstrating the policy&amp;rsquo;s capacity to incentivise a variety of climate mitigation methods and co-benefits, and the policy&amp;rsquo;s adaptability in diverse geographic settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="three-key-milestones"&gt;Three Key Milestones&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="partnering"&gt;Partnering&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The initial phase focuses on establishing collaborations with recognized NGOs and creating GCR think tanks across multiple countries. These think tanks will facilitate public-private partnerships involving governments, low-carbon technology firms, and nonprofit organizations with sponsorship arrangements.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Founder's Message</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/founders-message/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/founders-message/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="founders-message"&gt;Founder&amp;rsquo;s Message&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;The Global Carbon Reward is a citizen-led initiative to protect the climate, communities and ecosystems.&amp;rdquo; — Dr. Delton Chen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id="welcome"&gt;Welcome&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Delton Chen founded the Global Carbon Reward Initiative based on using a carbon reward (XCR) to mobilize climate action globally. According to the page, this instrument serves multiple purposes: economic stimulus, ecosystem service payments, and long-term investment. Crucially, the reward market differs from existing carbon markets because it avoids carbon offsetting entirely.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Our Logo</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-logo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/our-logo/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="our-logo"&gt;Our Logo&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://globalcarbonreward.org/images/gcr-logo.svg" alt="Global Carbon Reward logo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The official Global Carbon Reward emblem is provided above in scalable SVG format so you can reference it consistently across decks, presentations, and articles. Right-click/tap to download or &lt;a href="https://globalcarbonreward.org/images/gcr-logo.svg"&gt;open the file directly&lt;/a&gt; for inclusion in branding materials.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Global Carbon Reward logo contains four major symbolic elements designed to represent the organization&amp;rsquo;s climate and economic mission.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="four-key-elements"&gt;Four Key Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="1-the-letter-c"&gt;1. The Letter &amp;ldquo;C&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Represents elemental carbon and symbolizes greenhouse gas mitigation rather than pollution. The blue color signifies &amp;ldquo;the Earth&amp;rsquo;s atmosphere during the day.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>About GCR</title><link>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/carbon-rewards/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://globalcarbonreward.org/about/carbon-rewards/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="about-gcr"&gt;About GCR&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content goes here&amp;hellip;
Here&amp;rsquo;s some content&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>